声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Requiem校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：sealovemoon  憨妹 闲逛
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
哇哦! 你他妈混帐!
Ow! Son of a bitch!
-你他妈干什么?  -你他妈干什么?
-What are you doing?  -What are you doing?
我的膝盖...你差点打碎了我的膝盖骨!
You practically busted my knee.
你跟踪我?
Are you stalking me now?
跟踪你? 我是在保护你
Stalking you? I was protecting you.
怎么保护 南方人的保护法?
From what, Southern perverts?
是  随你怎么说
Yeah, whatever.
真不敢相信
I can't believe you.
还没那么糟
It's not that bad.
这是我的膝盖  我说多糟就有多糟
It's my knee. I'll tell you how bad it is.
不管怎样  先问你
What the hell
你在这周围晃来晃去干什么呢?
are you doing all the way out here,anyway?
大伙们吃的很多
Everyone's been eating a lot.
这是唯一一个树上的 果子没被摘光的地方
This is the only place the trees aren't picked clean.
是 但你不应该一个人来这儿 都发生那样的事了
You shouldn't be here alone, not after...
我不会有事的  我会管好我自己
No, I'm fine. I can take care of myself.
当然 "我不需要保护 我能管好我自己
Oh, of course. "I don't need protecting.I can take care of myself.
我能管好我自己
I can take care of myself.
我是Kate 我会扔石头"
Me Kate. Me throw rock."
怎么了 又闻到血腥味了?
What, you smell blood on the wind?
你没听到吗?
You don't hear that?
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
我要浸泡一下我疼痛的膝盖
I need to soak my sore knee.
来吧 雀斑女
Come on, Freckles.
经历了岛上这么多事
After all we've been through on this damn island,
难道还不应该好好享受一番?
don't we deserve something good?
什么 你不愿来?
What, you're gonna say no?
你是那种眼光短浅
Are you some sort of navel-gazing, no-fun, mopey type?
毫无乐趣 极度无聊的那类人?
no-fun, mopey type?
棒极了
Well.
有点冷
It's chilly.
来吧 妞!
Come on, girl! Whoo-hoo!
感觉好极了 是吧?
It's nice, huh?
你说呢?
What you got?
来 我们爬到岩石上去
Come on, let's go to the rock.
你没事吧?
Hey, are you okay?
没事!
Yeah.
你呢?
You?
没事 我得潜下去核查一下
Yeah. I'm gonna go check 'em out.
-核查什么?  -看他们身上有什么东西
-Check 'em out for what?  -See what they got on 'em.
Sawyer!
我给自己弄到一只钱包
Hey! Got myself a wallet.
-你真令人作呕  -他不会想念它了
-You're disgusting. -He ain't gonna miss it.
帮我把那只箱子弄上来
Help me with that case.
我令人作呕  你就不了?
Oh, I'm disgusting, but you're not?
那本来就是我的
It's mine.
不会钥匙还在你身上吧?
You wouldn't happen to have your key on you, would you?
这箱子不是你的 对吧?
That case ain't yours, is it?
不对
No.
好吧...
Well.
你不会介意的吧 如果我把它...
You wouldn't mind if I just...
拿走
Take it.
我不在乎
I don't care.
事情看起来并非这样
That's not what it looks like.
关于这箱子 你有什么要说的吗 雀斑女?
Something you want to tell me about this suitcase?
拿走吧
Take it.
东西都快被冲光了!
Everything is washing out to sea!
太不正常了
This can't be normal.
潮水来得如此突然...
The tide shifting so suddenly.
在这么短的时间里涨得这么高
Rising in so short a time.
这儿不正常的事情多着呢
There's a lot not normal around here.
按照这海滩被冲蚀的程度
The rate this beach is eroding,
机身得在水下呆好几天
the fuselage is going to be underwater in days.
黄昏前 我们得把所有东西从海滩搬走
We need to get all this stuff off the beach before nightfall.
我只希望海岸的上升会带来些变化
I hope moving up the coast will make a difference.
如果大伙都搬到内地去 事情是肯定会有变化的
It'd make a difference if everyone moved inland.
我想你会发现 以后人们进丛林会很谨慎的
I think you'll find people slightly wary of entering the jungle
孕妇发生了这样的事
after what happened to the pregnant girl,
更不用说那东西了
not to mention whatever that thing is.
Sayid...
我要你把那个法国女子Rousseau带过来
I need you to take me back to the French woman, Rousseau.
Claire还在某人手上
Claire's still out there.
而Rousseau提到过岛上还有...
Now, Rousseau mentioned that there are...
...其他人
...others on this island.
-她精神失常了  -你自己听到她这么说了
-Her mind is gone.  -You heard them.
-我不知道我听到了什么  -你说你....
-I don't know.  -You said that you...
风 Jack 是风玩的小把戏
The wind. It was the wind playing tricks.
好吧 那你从她那儿带回来的那些纸怎么说?
Then what about the papers that you took from her then?
那些文件 地图...我是说 有什么我们可以...
Documents, maps. Isn't there...
我擅长计算和解码
I'm skilled at mathematics,
但这些等式我还从没看到过
but these are beyond anything I've ever seen.
地图和图表上有一些法文注解
There are these notes in French accompanying the maps and diagrams.
如果我能够把它们翻译过来的话
If I could translate them,
或许就能够搞明白很多事情 但...
I might be able to make sense of it, but...
怎么?
What?
也许有些东西还是不要翻译的好
Perhaps some things are best left untranslated.
是吗?
Yeah?
或许你应该过去和他聊聊那事
Maybe you should tell him that.
很高兴看到你在干一些比较有"建设性"的事情
You're doing something productive.
你去哪了?
Where have you been?
"我去哪了" 什么意思?
What do you mean?
过去的四天里  你和Locke在太阳上升之前就离开了
You and Locke have been leaving before sunrise
到天黑才回来
and coming back after dark.
你们在干什么?
What are you doing out there?
他是你新认识的男朋友?
Is he your new boyfriend?
我们在找Claire
We're looking for Claire.
我知道已经没有线索了 没人知道该去哪儿找
I thought there was no trail, that no one knew where to look.
哦 是的 但至少我们在做一件事
Yeah, at least I'm doing something.
你没看到大伙是怎么看我们的吗?
Don't you see the way they look at us?
他们都没认真的看我们 我们只是个笑话而已
We're a joke.
我正努力给大家作贡献
I'm trying to contribute something.
而你...你一点用都没有
And you're just... you're useless.
好 Ryan小姐  请把身份证给我
Okay, Miss Ryan, if you'll just give me some ID,
我们要填贷款申请表
we'll get started on your loan app.
好 给
Okay. Here you go.
那么 你去新墨西哥州干什么呢?
So, what brings you to New Mexico?
去工作
My work.
什么样的工作?
What line of work is that?
我是个摄影师
I'm a photographer.
你拍什么?
What do you photograph?
我被委任为一本茶几书拍插图
I've been commissioned for a coffee table book.
拍一些小镇的旧剧院的照片
Pictures of old theaters in small towns.
在Rio Doso有一家很不错
There's a fantastic one down in Ruidoso.
你不要错过了 就在主道旁边
You can't miss it. It's off the main road.
我用完以后
Well, if I end up using it,
我一定会来感谢你的 Hutton...先生
I'll have to make sure I give you an acknowledgement, Mr... Hutton.
Mark
大家都给我趴下!
Everyone down
趴在地上!
on the ground now!
不要! 你不要想了! 我们行动!
Don't even think about it! Let's go!
闭嘴 到那边去!  行动!
Shut up and move over there! Let's go!
后面有谁?  我看到你了!
Who's back there? I see you!
好 大个子 给我滚到这边来!
Big boy, get your ass down there!
出来!  出来!  快!
Get out! Let's go!
好!  在那边不要动!
All right! Hold it right there!
好  这位小姐起来  到那边去!
All right, girlie, get up and get over there!
动作快! 快! 呆那儿! 就那儿!
Let's go! Move! Stay there!
趴在地上 娘们!
Get down on the ground, bitch!
你是不是经理?
Are you the manager?
我问你  你是不是经理?
I said, are you the manager?
是的
Yes.
很好  在我动手杀人之前
Good. Now let's open the money cage now
把钱库的门打开
before people start getting killed.
不要看着我!看地板!
Don't look at me! Look at the floor!
趴下!
Down right now!
我说了 趴下!
I said, down!
我抓到你了
Gotcha.
放开我
Get off of me.
天  我讨厌争位置  宝贝儿
I hate to bicker about positions,
但我想  你喜欢在上面
but I think you're the one on top.
也许你根本就不是冲着那只箱子来的
Maybe you're not here for the case at all.
女人
Ow! Woman!
如果你想动粗 说就行了
If you wanted to play rough, all you had to do was say so.
你想要再试一下?
You wanna try for it again?
给我
Give it to me.
这儿距离赤道很近
We're quite close to the equator.
比你以前晒的太阳要强烈很多
The sun might be stronger than what you're used to.
我底子很好
I have a pretty good base.
我有件事要问你
There was a matter I was going to ask you about.
什么?
What?
我需要你的帮助
I need a favor.
我要你帮我翻译一些我从 Rousseau那儿带回来的文件
I need your help translating papers I took from Rousseau
-Rousseau是谁?  -那个法国女子
-Who's Rousseau?  -The Frenchwoman.
我们收到求救信号的那个人
The distress call we intercepted.
我老哥叫你来的?
Did my brother put you up to this?
你老哥?
Your brother?
不
No.
这些文件有一些用法语注解的等式
The papers contain equations with notations in French.
如果我能搞懂这些等式的含义
If I can understand the notations...
抱歉 我做不了
Sorry, I can't do it.
但你是岛上唯一一个会说法语的人
You're the only person who speaks French.
-我几乎不会说法语  -拜托了 Shannon
-I barely speak French.  -Please, Shannon.
能不能至少试一下?
Can you at least try?
混帐
Son of a bitch.
你在浪费时间 老兄
You're wasting your time, man.
如果你能打开这把锁
If you pick the lock on a Halliburton,
我就背你飞会洛山矶
I'll put you on my back and fly.
你先给自己找好飞机跑道吧 老爹
You better find yourself a runway, daddy,
因为没有我打不开的锁
'cause there ain't a lock I can't pick.
他要干什么?
What's he trying to do?
打开这把锁?!
Pick the lock on a Halliburton.
祝你好运吧
Good luck.
要打开这箱子 只能纯粹靠力 老兄
The only way you're gonna open that case is with pure force,
靠冲击速度
impact velocity.
什么意思?
What's that mean?
你得用一些坚硬的物质击打它 比如大锤 斧头
You gotta hit it with something hard like a sledgehammer. Or the axe.
拿到了
You got it.
是的 拿着
Yeah. Right there.
去那儿有没什么近路?
Isn't there an easier way to get there?
近路不一定好
The easiest way isn't always the best.
有没有人看到你拿这东西?
Did anybody see you take it?
没有 我想应该没有
No. I don't think so.
-到底有没有?  -什么?
-Well, which is it?  -Sorry?
是"没有"  还是"我想没有"?
"No," or "I don't think so"?
没有
No.
很好 开始工作吧
Good. Let's get to work.
你好啊  Charlie
Hello, Charlie.
对了 这些天你不怎么说话
Oh, that's right. You're not talking much these days.
但这并不意味着你得变的无礼啊
But it doesn't mean you get to be rude.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
大伙都在帮忙把营地般得高一些 除了你
Everybody else is helping us move the camp up the beach, except for you.
真的 假的?
Are you serious?
你以为岛上只有你一个人有事情伤心吗?
You think you're the only one with something to be sad about?
孩子 我有更加另人伤心的故事要讲给你听
I got sob stories for you,
所以你能不能帮我抬另一头?
so why don't you grab the other end of this thing and help me?
好吗?
Well?
快
Come on.
冲击速度...
Impact velocity...
物理学!吃我屁弹
Physics, my ass.
好吧
All right.
混...
Son of a...
难以置信
Unbelievable.
你别想拿走
Don't even think about it.
该死的 雀斑女 我知道你想要
Hell, Freckles, I knew you wanted it.
没想到你这么想要这东西
I just didn't know how bad.
你就不能来点新招 啊!
You're gonna have to come up with a new move. Ah!
老天
God.
行了!好了 这么做太傻了
Okay! Okay, this is just silly.
等等
Hold on.
我有个建议...
I got a proposition for you.
你告诉我里面什么东西 我就把它给你
You tell me what's inside, and I'll give it to you.
你说真的?
Are you serious?
当然 我又打不开这箱子
Hell, no way to open the damn thing.
此刻 我关心的就是满足一下我的好奇心
At this point, all I care about is satisfying my own curiosity.
放松 宝贝儿
Oh! Easy, sweetheart.
我才不管里面什么东西
I don't really care what it is.
让我极度感兴趣的是 为什么这对你这么重要
What's burning me up is why it means so much to you.
最后一个机会
Last chance.
好吧
All right.
把钥匙给我
Give me the key now.
我已经问得烦了
I'm tired of asking nice.
把钱库的钥匙给我
Give me the money cage key now.
反正你会杀了我 我为什么要给你...
You're going to kill me. Why would I...
你以为我们是来谈判的啊?
You think we're having a conversation here? Huh?
大家给我安静!想回家吗?
Everybody be cool! Do you wanna go home?
别看着我!看着地板!
Don't look at me! Look at the floor!
大家不要慌 都给我趴好了
Everybody calm. Stay down.
听着 我不会再问你了 我要那把钥匙!
Listen to me, I am not gonna ask you again. I want that key!
-我可以制服他  -什么?
-I can take him.  -What?
那个高个子 他没看着我们 我可以把他拿下
The tall guy, he's not watching us.
只能趁现在 否则没机会 把头低下
It's now or never. Keep your head down.
小心!
Hey! Watch out!
拣起来!
Pick it up!
拣起来!  打他!  打他!
Pick it up! Shoot him!
你怎么回事?  开枪!
What's wrong? Shoot!
掩护!
Cover him!
打他!  打他!
Shoot him! Shoot him!
拉下保险销!
Turn off the safety!
把枪给我!
Gimme that.
在另一边!  拉下保险销!
It's on the side! Turn it off!
我不知道怎么使用枪!
I don't know how to use a gun!
你要吃子弹吗 肥仔?  恩?
You wanna get shot, fat boy? Huh?
-好 小英雄  -别 求你 别
-Okay, hero.  -No, please, don't.
闭嘴!让我们俩谈谈 恩?  里面 走!
Shut up! Let's you and me go talk. Huh? Right in here. Let's go.
"我不知道怎么用枪"?
"I don't know how to use a gun"?
-太经典了  -是的
-That's classic.  -Yeah.
你从没提到过数学
You never said anything about math.
你管法语 我管数学
You worry about the French. I'll take care of the math.
我做不了
I can't do this.
如果你能集中精力去做 我知道你行的 Shannon
If you really put your mind to it, I know you can.
你哪儿学的法语?
Where did you learn to speak French?
我认识这个家伙
I knew this guy.
这个家伙?
This guy?
在法国的St. Tropez  我在那儿住了一段时间
In France, in St. Tropez. I kind of lived there for a while.
他们说这是学外语最好的一种方法
Well, they say that is the best way to learn a foreign language.
好吧
All right.
我看看
Let me see.
那么...
So...
这是什么  这是干什么用的?
What is this? What is it for?
头疼
A headache.
酷
Oh. Cool.
好吧
All right.
Jack
我们遇到个问题
We got a problem.
我们遇到了问题 还是...
We have a problem, or...
你遇到了问题?
...you have a problem?
Jack 你是唯一一个了解我的人
Jack, you're the only one who knows about me.
在我离开去悉尼之前
Before I left for Sydney,
押送我的那位长官有只银色的箱子
the marshal who was escorting me, he had this silver case.
航空局不让他把箱子带到飞机上
The airline wouldn't let him bring it on the plane.
说服他们允许他带枪已经很困难了
It was hard enough trying to convince them to let him wear a gun.
但那只箱子...他们还是允许他带上飞机了
But the case, they made him check it.
箱子里有什么东西?
What was in the case?
一些旅行经费 还有他的一些私人物品
Some traveling money. Some of his personal stuff.
还有一把4.9毫米 和一些弹药
And four 9 millimeters with a few boxes of ammo.
枪
Guns.
那么 箱子现在在哪?
So, where is the case now?
Sawyer拿去了
Sawyer has it.
到现在为止 他还没打开 但...
He hasn't been able to open it.
-我俩走运  -他会的
-Lucky for us.  -He will.
迟早的事
Sooner or later.
那么 你要我怎么做?
So, what do you need me to do?
我知道钥匙在哪
I know where the key is.
他...长官把它放皮夹里了 皮夹在他后面那只口袋里
He... The marshal kept it in his wallet, in his back pocket.
我已经把他埋了 Kate
I buried him, Kate.
我知道
I know.
埋哪了?
Where?
告诉我箱子里还有什么?
So, what else is in the case?
箱子里还有其他什么东西 Kate?
What else is in the case?
你说的是实话?
That's the truth?
就是些枪
Just the guns.
如果你要我帮你 我们得一块儿打开那箱子
If you want my help, we're gonna open the case together.
好
Okay.
你笑什么?
Why are you smiling?
我在笑吗?
Am I?
你看起来很开心
You look happy.
我想你说对了
Well, I guess I must be then.
没理由好开心的 事情糟透了
There's no reason. Things are awful.
-还没那么糟  -我们被困在岛上
-They're not awful.  -We're stranded on an island.
-没人来救我们  -说不定呢
-No one's coming for us.  -You don't know that.
据我所知 丛林里有个爱吃人的东西
Well, what I do know is there's something in that jungle that eats people.
虽然我们好几周没听到它叫了
Just because we've not heard from it
但别以为它就不会肚子饿
doesn't mean it won't get hungry again.
我还知道有人要伤害我们
And I know there's a person or people that are trying to hurt us.
-Charlie  -还有...
-Charlie.  -And...
-没人责怪你  -什么?
-Nobody blames you.  -What?
对于Claire发生的事...
For what happened to Claire.
这并不是你的错
It's not your fault.
你能做的你都做了
You did everything that you could do,
还差点陪了命
and you came very close to dying yourself.
是
Yeah.
也许我还是死掉比较好
Maybe I should have died.
你知道我在想什么吗  Charlie?
You know what I think, Charlie?
你需要帮助
You need to ask for help.
谁会来帮我?
Who's gonna help me?
在你熔烧机身的时候
So why didn't you put him with the others?
你为什么不把他和其他人放在一起烧掉?
When you burned the fuselage?
因为我得埋了他
Because I needed to bury him.
你准备这么做了?
So you ready to do this?
是的 到现在为止 他们都已经胡思乱想了
Hell, yeah. By now their imaginations are running wild.
不要再隐瞒了
Don't hold back.
说出来的话他就不会告诉你了
He won't talk if the details are off.
你以及你的细节 Maggie
You and your details, Maggie.
-好吧 英雄...  -别 求你 不要
-Okay, hero.  -No, please, don't.
闭嘴!
Shut up!
大家放松!
Everybody just relax!
我说大家安静
I said quiet.
好 经理先生 你还是不肯说是吧?
Okay, Mr. Manager, you want to be a hard-ass?
保护一个不属于你的钱库?
Protect a vault that doesn't even belong to you?
好吧 得给点颜色瞧瞧了
Okay. There's gonna be consequences.
他会杀了我的
He's gonna kill me anyway.
我对天发誓 如果你再不闭嘴...
I swear, if you don't shut up.
给你三秒钟考虑时间把钥匙给我
You got three seconds to give me that damn key.
1...
One...
2...
Two...
3.
Three.
好吧
All right.
我给你
I'll give it to you.
很好 我们走
Good. Let's go.
呆在这边
Right around here.
我们走
Let's go.
-你没事吧?  -相对什么而言?
-You all right?  -Compared to what?
-你要我...  -不 我来
-You want me to...  -No. I'll do it.
哦  天
Oh, God.
-拿到了吗?  -是的
-Did you get it?  -Yeah.
钥匙不在里面
The key isn't in here.
没在?
It isn't?
不过 用钱包这招来骗我 你还真行
That was real good sleight of hand distracting me with the wallet.
松开
Open it.
-Jack...  -不要
-Jack...  -Don't.
不要
Don't.
"海...发光..."?  不 等等 不..
"The sea of sparkles?" No, wait. Um...
"改变着的散着银光的海洋"
"The sea of silver sparkles that change."
和最后一句一样
It's the same as the last one.
你确定?
Are you sure?
等式完全不同 这毫无关联
The equation is different. It doesn't relate.
你说得一点道理都没有
What you're saying doesn't make any sense.
好吧
Okay.
这个怎么说?
What about this one?
这应该是关于纬度和经度的
It should say something about latitude.
一些和星星有关的东西
Something about the stars.
好 给我一点思考空间 行吗?
Give me some room.
"靠近池塘...蓝色..."
"Next to the pond... blue..."
"蓝色水泥板--蓝色永恒"
Uh..."Blue eternity."
不 等等 不 呃.. "蓝色..无穷"
No, wait, no. Um, "Blue infinity."
"蓝色..无穷"
"Blue infinity."
感觉有什么东西很熟悉
There's something about this that is so familiar.
过去的一小时 你跟我
You've been telling me
说的几乎是一堆废话
what sounds very much like nonsense for the past hour,
现在又说很熟悉?
and now it seems familiar?
好 A: 我告诉过你我的法语糟透了
Okay, A: I told you that my French sucks.
B: 我没有胡说 行了吗?
And B: This isn't my nonsense, okay?
你有没想过  在这个神秘的岛上呆16年后
Do you ever think that after 16 years on Mystery Frickin' Island,
你朋友还会不适应吗?
your friend might not be quite adjusted?
这是个错误
This was a mistake.
是啊 你是不是听说了我很没用啊?!
Yeah. Haven't you heard? I'm completely useless.
Sawyer?
医生
Doctor.
有什么我能效劳的?
So, what can I do you for?
我就知道她会叫你来干这个苦活
Figured she'd get you to do her dirty work for her.
那么 怎么说 摔交决胜负?
So, what? We gonna wrestle for it?
不 你会把它给我的
No, you're gonna give it to me.
-是吗?  -是的
-Am I?  -Yeah.
我会把它给你?
I'm just gonna give it to you?
是的
Yeah.
我为什么会这么做?
Why would I want to do that?
头孢氨苄
Cephalexin.
哦?继续说
Yeah? Go on.
那是我给你用来治疗臂伤的抗生素
That's the antibiotic I'm giving you for the knife wound in your arm.
你还在治疗周期里
You're in the middle of a cycle.
现在 如果我继续给你药
If I keep giving you the pills,
你的病情会好转很快
you're gonna be as right as rain.
但如果我不给你药
But I'm gonna stop giving you the pills.
头两天 你会觉得你还不错
For two days you're gonna think you're all good.
然后伤口会开始发痒
Then it's gonna start to itch.
这以后 马上就伴有高烧
The day after, the fever will come
然后你就会发现手臂上下全是红条纹
and you'll see red lines running up and down your arm.
这之后不用一两天
Day or two after that...
你会求我把箱子拿走
...you'll beg me to take the case
还有求我把你的胳膊切掉
just to cut off your arm.
故事编得真好听 Jack
That's a nice story, Jack.
即使你说得都是真的
And even if it were true,
我也不相信你会这么做
I don't think you could do it.
你错了
You're wrong.
她告诉你里面有什么了?
She tell you what's inside?
是的 也没告诉我
Yeah, me neither.
希望你能在"山洞镇"挽回几条生命
Hope you got yourself some jaws of life back in Cave Town.
因为要搞清楚这娘们的事必须得这么做
That's what it's gonna take to pop this bitch.
我会想办法的
I'll figure something out.
我知道你认为你在帮她的忙
I know you think you're doing her a favor,
但不管她怎么跟你解释这件事
but however she talked you into doing this,
她一定在说谎 老兄
she lied, brother.
Jack?
我们得一起打开
We're gonna do this together.
为什么?
Why?
因为我说过我们要一起打开
Because that's what I said we'd do.
你还在等什么?
What are you waiting for?
快打开这该死的门!
Open the damn thing!
现在我们说了算 不要乱动
Hell, now we're talking. Don't move.
-不要 我...  -闭嘴
-Please don't. I...  -Shut up.
我让你们进来了 现在可以放女孩走了吧
I let you in. Now please let the girl go.
放女孩走?
Let the girl go?
老兄 你还不知道吧?
Man, you have no idea, do you?
设你圈套的就是这个女孩
The girl is the one who set you up.
这女孩选了这个银行
The girl picked this bank.
选了这个金库
Picked this vault.
整件事都是女孩的主意
This whole thing is the girl's idea.
-你要干什么?  -放松 Maggie
-What are you doing?  -Easy, Maggie.
装钱就是了
Just cleaning up after myself.
你开枪 我也开枪
You shoot, I shoot.
等等 什么?
Wait. What?
我说过了 别伤害任何人
I said no one gets hurt.
我知道你很冷漠 宝贝
I know you're cold, baby.
但你还不至于那么冷漠
But you're not that cold.
这他妈发生什么事了?
What the hell is going on here?
你向我开枪 你这狗娘们!
You shot me, you stupid bitch!
闭嘴  Jason
Shut up, Jason.
我告诉过你不要信任她!
I told you not to trust her!
我要850号保险柜的钥匙
I need the key to safety deposit box 850 now.
你是谁?
Who are you?
给我保险柜的钥匙
The key to the box now.
你要有两把钥匙才行...银行的  还有...
You need two keys, the bank's and...
既然你有顾客的钥匙 你为什么还要...
If you had the customer key, why...
我未被授权的
I'm not on the signatory card.
你唆使我这么做 就为了只保险柜?
You put me up to this to get into a safe deposit box?
我对天发誓 你最好杀了我  Maggie 因为如果你不...
I swear to God, you better kill me, 'cause if you don't...
我名字不叫Maggie 走吧
My name's not Maggie. Now go.
有什么要说的吗?
Anything you want to tell me?
那好吧
All right then.
是这个吗?
Is this it?
这就是你想要的?
Is this what you wanted?
这是什么?
What is it?
没什么
It's nothing.
-这是什么 Kate?  -你不会明白的
-What is it, Kate?  -You wouldn't understand.
我要事实
I want the truth.
就这个事实 这是什么?
Just this once. What is it?
这东西属于一个我喜欢的人
It belonged to the man I loved.
说实话
The truth.
这东西属于一个我喜欢的人!
It belonged to the man I loved!
不要再骗我了! 告诉我事实!
Stop lying to me! The truth!
我没骗你! 这是被我杀害的那个人的东西
It belonged to the man I killed!
你老伴是在飞机的尾舱里
Your husband was in the tail section of the plane.
是的
Yes, he was.
但是他会回来的
But he'll be back.
你觉得他还活着?
You think he's still alive?
我知道他活着
I know he is.
怎么知道?
How?
我就是知道
I just do.
这是一根在否认和信任之间的幸运线
It's a fine line between denial and faith.
线在我这一边 事情就会好很多
It's much better on my side.
帮帮我
Help me.
孩子...
Baby...
我不是那个可以帮助你的人
I'm not the one that can help you.
神甫
Heavenly father,
我们感谢你
we thank you.
感谢你让我们在今晚相聚
We thank you for bringing us together tonight.
我们请求你给Charlie指明方向...
And we ask, that you show Charlie the path...
在St.Tropez(法国城市)的那家伙
The guy from St. Tropez,
他有个孩子...
he had this kid.
一个真正的小人...
A real snot,
恨我的人
who hated me.
他叫Laurent
His name was Laurent.
他看这本电影
He watched this movie
反反复复 反反复复
over and over and over again,every day,
几乎每天 像孩子那样 900遍
all day, like kids do, 900 times.
这是一本有关鱼的卡通电影
It was the cartoon about fish.
你知道 用电脑制作的
你为什么要告诉我这些?
Why are you telling me this?
因为电影是用法语配音的
The movie was dubbed in French,
结尾的时候就有这首歌
and at the end, there was this song.
那些注解...
Those notations,
就是歌词
they're song lyrics.
而你的那位法国女子
And your French woman,
她就像Laurent一样
she's just like Laurent,
因为她反反复复 反反复复的写歌词
'cause she wrote them over and over again.
什么歌?
What's the song?
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====